Do you know my daughter,
Joey Delgado?
She said she would
wait for you here.
She went over there,
to the market.
The men who pushed me...
are there too.
It looks like they're chasing
a student around here.
I even helped her escape...
from those ugly men.
Where did she go?
There the one who is looking for
Miss Beautiful.
Let's split up.
Go back there.
Got you!
This is from that woman,
the one who bought from me.
Where is she?
Tell me where she went!
Looks like the woman
already got away!
Who are you?
Were you with the one
who shot my mommy?
Did you come here
to finish the job?
That kid must've fooled us.
There she is!
- Hey, get in the car!
- Let's go!
- Hey!
Mr. Limjoco knows me.
What's going on here, Matias?
You two know each other?
I'll explain everything to you.
What do you need
with the woman you're chasing?
Who are you? Are you her father?
Joey...
You're safe now.
My name is Jin Ho.
You think I don't know?
You've been following me
since last night!
Matias is my business partner.
I'm sorry, Mr. Dizon.
I wasn't really
going to shoot you.
Just call me Andrew.
I'm here on San Isidro Street.
My stalker saved me.
What stalker?
This is not my day.
Hey, come back here!
Joey, what was that?
Dad, he left!
My stalker left!
Where are you?
I'm coming to you.
Dad, just meet me
at your boarding house.
It's closer to you.
All right, I'll go home
right away after.
Oh, okay.
Okay, Dad.
Hon...
Where have you been?
The guests were looking for you.
And you, your nieces have been
looking for you too.
Oh, I was just talking
to your sibling.
What happened to you?
Why are you so dirty?
Even your back,
it's filthy.
What happened to you?
Oh, I must have
brushed against something.
Oh, tell the kids
I'll make it up to them.
I just really,
really have to go.
Okay, sure.
Brother, please take care
of sister and mom.
Always.
I'll go now.
Okay.
Take care.
- Bye.
- Okay.
Hon, I'll just talk to
the caterers, okay?
There's a small problem.
- Okay.
- All right.
Joey!
Why is that with you?
Where's Joey?
Joey!
What are you doing here?
Oh...
Why are you looking for Joey?
Did something happen?
What happened to your face?
Did you get into a fight?
I'll just wait for Joey outside.
Wait, Miguel!
You're not answering
my questions again.
Why are you so worried
about Joey?
Are you hiding something?
I have no idea
what's going on anymore.
If I tell you,
will you even believe me?
Or will you believe Andrew Dizon
more than your own husband?
My husband doesn't even
talk to me.
He always says
he's buried in work...
but it turns out
he's with another woman.
Sir.
Aren't you Major Miguel
Delgado's partner?
Yes, why?
I was hoping I could get
his contact number.
Sir!
The search warrant
has been issued.
We're coordinating with the
Manila police force
to search Major Delgado's
belongings.
We expedited this
because we don't want him
getting rid of any evidence
connecting him to
Sergeant Orbos' death.
Yes, Sir.
Follow me to the office.
What are you doing?
You can't open my dad's car!
Joey?
That's Joey.
Joey.
- Sir, what is this?
- Joey?
Joey...
- Joey...
- What's going on here?
They want to open dad's car.
They're accusing him
of all sorts of things.
Miguel Delgado,
we have a warrant
to search your vehicle.
Give us the key.
What?
Yes?
Sir, someone wants
to speak with you.
It's Andrew Dizon.
All right, let him in.
What do you need?
Oh...
Is it true that...
Major Delgado
is the number one suspect
in Orbos' murder?
Oh right, you hate him.
Not at all. I'm just curious...
why Major Delgado...
is your number one suspect.
What could be his motive?
You know I can't tell you that,
the investigation is ongoing.
But rest assured,
we're following protocol.
And we have strong reasons
for what we're doing.
This isn't easy for us either.
He's one of our own, after all.
Wait, what warrant?
What are you talking about?
For what?
Your husband is a suspect
in the death...
of Staff Sergeant Ramon Orbos.
Miguel...
is this true?
Are you doubting me?
- Then what are they saying?
- Mom...
What do you want me to do?
Hand over the key?
Here.
Dad...
If they don't find anything...
- will you trust me?
- Search.
Will you stop it!
Dad, wait!
You don't need to search
my dad's car...
because I have proof...
he's not the one
who killed Ramon Orbos!
Wait.
I can prove my dad is innocent.
Wait a second.
Wait, wait...
Joey, what are you looking for?
Where is it?
Wait!
Peter knows!
Peter knows.
- Yes, it's true.
- We have proof.
Dad, this is what
I'm going to give you.
This is the evidence...
that will clear your name.
Wait.
It was really here.
Where is it?
It's really gone.
Excuse me.
Where is it?
- Joey...
- I put it here!
Joey, what are you looking for?
Mom, I put it...
Joey...
Dad, I'm sorry.
I really put it here.
I'm sorry.
Dad, I'm sorry.
Joey...
Don't talk to anyone.
The evidence you're holding...
is the reason
they're chasing you.
You weren't careful.
Andrew saw you...
and you even pulled out a gun.
I held back, Boss.
Your brother-in-law
just wouldn't stop.
You know me.
I don't like being
at a disadvantage.
You're lucky he trusts me.
Whatever I say, he believes.
We really are business partners,
aren't we?
Is this registered, Major?
Dad...
What is that?
Is that yours?
That gun isn't mine.
I've only just seen it now.
I only came...
because I knew you prefer
receiving good news in person.
No one will block our operation
in Bolagos anymore.
Parak already made sure...
Delgado gets imprisoned.
That gun doesn't belong to me.
Just go to the precinct
and explain yourself there.
You'll be taken to Bolagos.
Wait a minute, I have evidence.
You can't take my father!
Remember what I told you.
I don't want you to get hurt,
Joey.
But, Dad...
I'll come with you.
Dad...
Don't hurt my family.
Dad , Dad , I have evidence.
- I'll give it to you.
- Joey!
Remember what I told you.
Come with me.
Dad, wait...
Dad...
Wait a minute, I have evidence.
Dad!
I have evidence!
You can't take my father.
Dad!
Peter, you know I have evidence,
right?
- I have a video!
- Yes!
He didn't kill Ramon Orbos!
- Let's go, come on.
- Joey!
Let's go.
Wait! Dad!
Mom, they can't take dad.
Parak sent a message.
Delgado is on his way
to Bolagos.
That's good to hear.
We didn't make a mistake
in choosing Parak.
He's been very valuable to us.
Speaking of mistakes...
There's something you need
to know about Lisa.
She also has a problem?
Someone intervened,
that's why the woman
managed to escape.
And you still haven't
seen her face?
The hood of her red jacket
covered her face.
I was about to get closer,
Madam.
I almost got her!
But suddenly a car arrived,
and the woman got inside
the car.
That's why I didn't catch her.
Oh...
Is that so?
What's the use of your feet...
if that's the case, huh?
Oh, I'm sorry, Madam!
Madam!
Someone saw her...
while torturing Ramon,
and they caught it on video.
And?
They're already working on...
finding the witness...
and getting the video.
So far, no news yet.
Call Lisa.
Yes, Boss.
That's enough! Ma'am!
Hello?
I'll be there.
I'll call your Godfather Diego
to join us in Bolagos.
And maybe he can help.
But Joey, I don't know
how to deal
with your father now.
What are you saying, Mom?
Do you really believe that
dad could do that?
Mom, dad is not a murderer,
and that's not his gun!
I know all that!
He doesn't have any other gun!
Joey, my child...
Mom, didn't I tell you?
I have proof!
I have a video that will prove
that dad is innocent!
I just can't find it right now,
but I do have a video!
Joey, what are you going to do?
I'll find the video,
I'll give it to dad.
Joey!
I'll help Joey.
I'll talk to her.
Sir, Sir!
Can I ask for a statement?
Did you kill
Sergeant Ramon Orbos?
Sir! Sir! Are you part of...
a drug trafficking syndicate?
Sir, just give us an answer.
Sir?
Did you kill
Sergeant Ramon Orbos?
Are you part of a drug
trafficking syndicate?
Sir, Sir, give us an answer,
Sir!
Sir, did you kill him?
Sir, Sir, Sir!
Sir, did you kill
Sergeant Ramon Orbos, Sir?
Sir!
Sir, give us a statement, Sir!
- Yes, Elai?
- Hello, Boss?
They say Delgado
has been arrested.
I know, I'm here
at Bolagos Precinct.
Okay, good.
We'll follow there.
That's where we're going
to do our livestream.
No, no. Don't.
There are a lot
of reporters here.
I want to tell the story
from a different angle.
Anong angle?
Joey, there's really nothing.
What do you mean by nothing?
It's just there!
I'll take it from here!
Just relax.
We'll find it, okay?
Joey...
Ah, Mom, wait.
I'll fix this later.
I just need to find
the flash drive.
Your Godfather is on his way.
Mom, it's just right here.
Joey...
Joey, I know what your father
is going through is scary.
But if he's not really guilty,
the truth will come out.
Is this yours?
Your father brought it
when he came here earlier.
He saw it outside.
Maybe it fell in your stuff.
In the market...
What?
Mom, I have to go back
to the market.
I think I left
the flash drive there.
What about your godfather?
I'll follow right away.
When I get back, I'll have
the evidence
that will free dad.
Oh...
Peter, let's go to the market.
Let's go.
Joey...
The lab will analyze this gun.
But so far,
this is the same caliber
that killed Sergeant Orbos.
Sir, that gun is not mine.
Believe me.
I can't just take your word
for it, Major Delgado.
You know the process.
Sir, I know I've said
a lot of things,
but does it have
to come to this?
I don't like what you're
showing, Major Delgado!
This isn't personal.
We're acting on the evidence...
found in your car!
Sir, I was set up.
That gun isn't mine.
Maybe it was planted
by those who arrested me.
This guy is crazy!
Stop it, Major Delgado.
You're insulting our comrades.
Cruz, take him in.
Sir, I didn't kill Orbos.
That's an order!
Sir...
Sir, I was set up!
Are you sure about
what you're saying?
Of course, Boss Idol.
I heard it clearly.
Chief said the gun
that killed Orbos...
was found in
Major Delgado's car.
Oh, okay, Dante.
Thank you.
Ah, okay, thank you very much
for this, too.
Oh...
It seems Delgado will no longer
get away with his crimes.
Do you really think
he killed Orbos?
That's what the evidence says.
But isn't it so convenient,
Elai...
that the gun he used
to kill Orbos
is in his car?
It's been days.
Why hasn't he
thrown it away yet?
I don't know.
Maybe he's just stupid.
He didn't think about it.
Elai, he's smart.
He's not that stupid
to commit that mistake.
Wait, are you saying
Delgado is innocent?
Maybe you've forgotten,
it was you exposed him.
I know, I know...
but at this point...
my hunch is different.
What if Major Delgado
was set up?
Huh...
You traitor!
You should know by now...
that Matias' loyalty is with me.
So it's only right for him to
report your mistake.
That wasn't a mistake.
It was an accident.
You were careless, that's why
someone took a video of you.
Let me remind you, Lisa.
I took you in to be
an asset in our operation.
But if you'll be exposed,
you will become a liability.
That's not going to happen.
That's why I'm doing
all I can...
to find that girl...
and get the video back.
Make sure of it.
Boss, he's here.
There he is.
The man of the hour.
Good job, Parak.
Executioner.
The first thing I destroyed
was Delgado's name.
No one will believe him anymore.
Did he really drive me away?
I was hurt too.
I have evidence
that can help dad.
I just need to find...
that flash drive.
Flash drive?
I'm doing something
to clear my name.
I'm getting help from Boss Idol.
- You're so shameless!
- Hey, Joey, don't.
Trust me.
Never say die.
But she keeps telling me...
she has proof.
She'll prove Miguel's innocence.
Someone saw her torturing Ramon.
I can find it on my own.
Can you really do it?
I need her to tell me
where the video was taken.
Don't worry, I'll find
Theresa very soon.
You were looking for evidence.
It's a video.